♪♪
Dad, just get back
in your car and leave.
Or what?
You stay away from my mother.
Get out of my way, Dan.
I'm warning you!
Don't go in there.
Anything you say can and will be
used against you in a court of law.
If you cannot afford an attorney,
the court will appoint one for you.
Oh, Danny.
Do you understand what
I just told you, Danny?
I understand.
Please don't take
my boy. Please.
I'm sorry, ma'am.
Please stand aside.
Mom, it's OK, it's all
right. You stay here.
Grandma.
- Hey, Ben?
- Yeah.
I brought you that book...
Better Health Through
Fruits and Vegetables.
Oh, good.
- You're not going to eat that.
- I bet I can.
What about Health Through
Fruits and Vegetables?
Well...
Chicken dipped in batter and
drenched in oil isn't healthy.
I know, but I get
to have some fun.
Every time I turn on the
TV, I see a news report
about how something I've
eaten all my life is going to kill me
and the five or six things
that are still OK are dangerous
because of the stuff they spray
on it or pour on it or wrap it in.
The air's no good.
The water's no good.
The ozone is going like 60-cent gasoline,
so I'll worry about it all tomorrow.
What's that?
It's going to be dumplings.
You can't eat dumplings.
I bet I can.
Not without gravy.
I make terrific gravy.
- You're invited.
- Hmm.
- Would you get that?
- Sure.
Hello?
Christine? Slow down.
Christine, that's terrible.
How is my mom?
She's hanging in there, Danny.
Is somebody with her?
She shouldn't be alone.
Your grandmother is with her.
Danny...
your mom told me
that you shot your dad
because you thought he was
going inside the house to kill her.
No, no, no. He said that
he was going to kill her.
I knew that he meant that.
Sometimes people threaten
terrible things when they're angry,
but later on, when they calm down.
They never really meant what they said.
Not my dad.
If he said he was going
to do something, he did it.
Like what?
What kinds of things would
he threaten and then do?
My dad wanted dinner on
the table every night at 6 P.M.
He told my mom that meant
6:00... Not 6:05 or 6:10...
And the next time dinner
wasn't ready at 6:00...
he'd bash her face in.
Your father physically
abused your mother?
He broke her leg.
Your mother told me that she
slipped and fell down the stairs.
No. He pushed her.
That's... That's
why they separated.
He'd hit her or...
throw things at her.
He used to lock
her in the closet.
I remember lying
in bed at night,
hearing her scream and cry.
I remember one time he hit her
because she threw out the
newspaper before he could read it.
Your mom never
told me any of this.
She didn't tell anybody.
She wanted
everybody to think that...
our family was normal.
She even made excuses for him.
How long had all
this been going on?
Forever.
The last few months,
it just got worse.
He got madder and madder.
I had to shoot him.
The problem is, Danny,
you didn't have to shoot him.
If you thought your father
was going to kill your mother,
why didn't you get
her out of the house?
I tried. She wouldn't go.
My dad wouldn't let her work,
she had no money of her own.
Where was she supposed to go?
- You could have called the police.
- I did.
The police asked me
if he was standing there
waving a gun or anything like that...
Was there any immediate danger?
I said no.
They said that they needed more
reason than a threat to arrest him,
and that if my mom
wanted him to stay away,
she'd have to file
a restraining order.
Yeah, that's standard procedure.
Can you help me?
I'll sure try.
Um, will you do me a favor?
If I can.
Will you tell my
grandmother I'm sorry?
First, I'm going to tell Ben
everything you told me.
And then we'll see about
getting the charges reduced.
No prosecutor would
push for first degree murder
if he heard what you just
told me about your dad.
Mr. Connolly, were you surprised
the jury reached a
guilty verdict this quickly?
Surprised. Delighted.
Hungry. Sleepy. That just
about covers all my emotions.
Ben, I wish you had seen
me in that courtroom today.
- That good, huh?
- Better.
I just threw a shutout in there.
- Hey.
- Excuse me.
Um, I hear you've been
assigned the Danny Hayes case.
That's a fact.
You're not thinking of
defending him, are you?
I'm considering it.
I'm surprised.
You generally don't defend
people who confess to murder.
Ordinarily I don't, but, uh...
I don't think this is
a murder one case.
You're kidding.
Frank Hayes had a
history of violent behavior.
He was a wife-beater.
That wasn't in
the police report.
Well, his wife didn't report it.
But Frank Hayes told his
wife that he would kill her
if he found her in
the house that night.
And given his history
of violent behavior,
Danny believed him.
Danny was just
defending his mother.
And that gave him license to
just shoot his father in cold blood?
- I didn't...
- Ben.
I'll grant you I'm no
Harvard Law graduate,
but where I went to school,
if a kid sits hiding in a garage for
two hours with a gun in his hand,
then shoots his unarmed father
the minute he gets out of his car,
well, that's murder
one in a very big way.
He didn't shoot him the
minute he stepped out of his car.
He was trying to get him
not to go in the house.
He was protecting his mother,
not going to shoot his father.
But he did shoot his father.
I'm surprised at you.
This kid handed you a line,
and you swallowed it
hook, line, and sinker.
I believe what Danny told me.
Ben, your client was
lying in wait for his victim.
You know that constitutes
extraordinary circumstances.
It's wrong to put this boy
on trial for murder one.
Well, we'll see
what a jury thinks.
See you in court, Counselor.
Jackass.
Mr. Connolly, are you ready
to give your opening statement?
I am, Your Honor.
It is June 10th of this
year, ladies and gentlemen.
It is the last few minutes
of Frank Hayes' life.
As he exits his car
and he walks the five or seven feet
toward the door leading to his house...
Even as his hand
reaches for the knob...
gunshots shatter
the evening calm
and enter Frank Hayes' back,
to the left of the spine,
and lodge in his heart.
The evidence in this case will
show, beyond a reasonable doubt...
that some person very close to
Frank Hayes had come to hate him...
was waiting in the
garage for him to arrive,
took aim with a
high-powered handgun...
and, without any justification
or provocation whatsoever,
killed him in cold, cold blood.
A plotted, planned and premeditated
murder of a human being.
That person is seated
in this courtroom...
at that table, in that chair.
That person's name
is Daniel Hayes.
He is the son of Frank Hayes,
and he is the
defendant in this case.
Ladies and gentlemen, the
evidence you will hear speaks for itself.
The state asks only that
you listen to that evidence...
and you give us your verdict
in accordance with the law.
Mr. Matlock?
That was a very
convincing speech.
So, why don't we just convict
Danny Hayes of murder right now
and send him to prison
for the rest of his life?
Of course, you would
be disregarding the law,
but that's what my
distinguished colleague
apparently wants you to do.
He is absolutely
right about one thing.
Murder is never justified.
However, we do
have, in this country,
a thing called
"justifiable homicide".
Every state in
the Union allows it.
It's a law that simply means...
in defense of
another human being,
you, you, you, or Danny Hayes,
has the right to keep that
person from being killed.
We don't have to
sit on our hands.
Now, you're going
to hear evidence
that Frank Hayes was
not just an ordinary man
who lost his temper
once in a while.
This was a violent,
intolerant man
who frequently slapped,
beat, abused his wife.
And then, when his
temper reached its peak,
he made a promise that he
would return at a specified time
and take the life of
Danny Hayes' mother.
And Danny believed his father.
He took him at his word.
Frank Hayes was a
wife beater, abuser.
He would say he was
sorry, wouldn't do it again,
and then something would
set off this violent man.
And he said to his wife, "I'm
coming back here tomorrow,
"and if you're still here,
I'm going to kill you."
And Danny believed him.
After you've heard
all the testimony,
I'm going to ask you to put
yourself in Danny's shoes.
Ask yourself...
"Would I defend my mother
"if I were certain
"that, in a matter of seconds,
"her life would be ended?"
Would you?
OK, there you go.
Eat your pie.
Oh, no, thanks. I'm not hungry.
Danny, you have to eat.
I don't want you looking
pale in the courtroom.
I dream about him every night.
I see his face, hear Mom crying.
I'm not surprised.
I'm very worried.
If your mother had just
called the cops once, twice...
Once... it would have helped.
At least your father's abuse
would have been on the record.
If you had left your name when
you called, that would have helped.
Wait, you don't believe me?
My belief isn't necessary
or even important.
Reasonable doubt.
There is no doubt
you shot your father.
We have to make the jury believe
that you felt you had to shoot
him to save another person's life.
Ain't nothing easy.
And this sure ain't.
Eat your pie.
Mr. Connolly, would
you like to proceed?
Thank you, Your Honor.
Mr. Blessing...
are you acquainted
with the defendant?
We went to high school together.
Do you recall an incident that
took place about a year ago
between you and the defendant
regarding a gold-plated pen?
Yeah, I'd call it an incident.
Will you elaborate
for the court, please?
Danny accused me
of stealing his pen.
Had you stolen it?
No. He found it later, scrunched
in the back of his car seat.
Mr. Blessing, when Mr. Hayes
suspected you had stolen his pen,
did he tell a teacher or take
you aside and talk to you?
Are you kidding? He
knocked the crap out of me.
He hit you?
He cracked my tooth.
What did you do to
provoke Mr. Hayes' rage?
Nothing. I was in
the locker room.
I was headed for the showers, and
he just came up and blindsided me.
You mean he attacked you
because he believed you had his pen
- and not because he had any proof?
- That's right.
Sounds to me like Daniel
Hayes has a hair-trigger temper.
Nothing further.
Mr. Matlock, your witness.
Mr. Blessing...
uh, have you ever
been in a fistfight before?
Yeah, lots of times.
Oh. Were you ever in a
fistfight with Mr. Hayes before?
Well, yeah.
What was that fight about?
He asked out my girlfriend.
Ohh, he made a
move on your girl.
That must have made you mad.
In that fight, who
threw the first punch?
Who threw the first punch?
I did, but he was asking...
No further questions.
Witness may step down.
You may call your next witness.
The state calls Sam
Parker to the stand.
Mr. Parker, you were
a close, personal friend
of Frank Hayes, were you not?
I knew Frank for 21 years.
He was my best friend.
In all those years
of friendship,
did you ever witness any violent
behavior from Frank Hayes?
- Never.
- See him uncontrollably enraged?
- Be physically abusive to anyone?
- No.
How about to his wife?
No way. Frank was a
really good husband.
How about his
relationship with his son?
- Did he ever talk to you about it?
- Sometimes.
He couldn't understand why
Danny hated him so much.
Do you recall the night
before Frank Hayes' death?
Yes. I spent part of
the evening with him.
We had dinner, and then
I drove him to his house.
Now, in your own words,
I'd like you to explain
the events of that evening, as
best you can remember them.
After Frank and
Christine had separated,
Frank and I started getting
together once a week for dinner.
Anyway, we were sitting
in this cafe that night,
and Frank started telling me
how much he missed Christine.
Finally, I told him
to stop telling me this
and get over and tell her.
Chris?
Chris, it's Frank.
Christine was wearing
a real sexy dress.
You could see she was mad
because Frank showed
up without calling.
Why didn't you call?
I've missed you, Chris.
Ask Sam here. You're
all I ever talk about.
You should have
called first, Frank.
Is everything okay, Chris?
Who are you?
Jack, this is my husband.
What's this guy
doing in my house?
Well, that's none of
your business, Frank.
You're the one who said
we should see other people.
What?
What the hell are
you talking about?
About then, Danny
came out of his room.
I think maybe I'd better go.
I'll call you later.
- Where are you going?
- To bed.
Chris, we've got to talk.
Frank started upstairs
to talk to Christine,
but she didn't want
any part of him.
You can't just barge into
this house any time you want.
Why not? I pay the bills.
Just get out of here, Frank.
I don't want to talk to you.
Christine...
That's when Danny blocked
his father's way upstairs.
You heard what she
said, Dad. Get out of here!
Get out of my way. This is
between your mother and me.
Don't you ever lay your
hand on me like that again.
Danny didn't have to throw
him downstairs like that.
Luckily, Frank wasn't hurt.
I helped him up and
told him we should go.
Did Frank Hayes make a
threat of any kind to his wife
before you left?
Yes, he did.
I'm not going to stand by while my
wife shares my bed with somebody else.
I want you moved
out of this house
by the time I come back
here tomorrow night.
Or what, Frank?
I'll kill you, that's what.
Mr. Parker, do you believe
that Frank Hayes literally meant
that he intended to return to
that house the following day
and kill his wife Christine?
Objection. Calls
for speculation.
This is hardly
speculation, Your Honor.
The witness had a lengthy
conversation with the victim
the moment they left the house.
- Then it's hearsay.
- Overruled.
The witness may
answer that question.
No, he wouldn't
have hurt Christine.
In fact, when we got to the
car, he broke down in tears.
He said he loved his Chris
and prayed to God they'd
be able to work things out.
I have nothing further.
Uh, Mr. Parker, I apologize.
I just can't quite remember
the name of the restaurant
where you and Frank had
dinner the night before he died.
Scully's Grill.
Oh. I believe that's
Scully's Bar and Grill, isn't it?
Yeah, actually I think it is.
So, did you and
your friend Frank
have some alcoholic
drinks along with dinner?
- Yes, I believe we did.
- How many?
- One or two.
- Or three or four?
No more than three.
Oh, so I guess you were feeling
no pain, maybe a little woozy.
I was perfectly fine.
Do you mean to tell me that
three strong alcoholic drinks
won't impair your perception of
things the way it does everybody else?
I remember that night
very clearly, Mr. Matlock.
Let me ask you
something, Mr. Parker.
You say that Frank was a
good and loving husband
who never physically
abused his wife.
That's right.
Uh, how often did you spend
an evening with the two of them?
Excuse me?
Well, in all the years
that you've known them,
how often would you
say you and your wife
spent an evening with
Frank and Christine Hayes?
I don't know.
Would it be closer
to one or a hundred?
Frank and I were buddies.
We used to hang out
together, not with our wives.
The truth is, you hardly spent
any time with the two of them,
so you couldn't know whether he
was a good and loving husband.
I knew Frank. You didn't.
You knew what he drank.
You knew what sports
he liked to bet on.
You knew what cars
he wanted to buy.
But you didn't have a
clue how he treated his wife
or how he got
along with his son.
That's not true.
Mr. Parker...
I'm sure you miss Frank.
I believe he was
your best friend,
and my guess is that
you'd feel a lot better
if his death were avenged.
Don't you dare
patronize me, damn it.
Mr. Parker...
Your Honor, he's trying
to twist everything around.
Danny hated Frank.
- Move to strike...
- He's glad he's dead.
Hey, shut up! You
don't know anything.
- Sit down, young man!
- He's lying!
Mr. Matlock, restrain your client,
or I'll have the bailiff remove him.
This is a beautiful garden.
Rose, Danny asked me to come by
and tell you that he loves you.
And he's sorry.
Danny says that
you were in the house
the night Frank came
home with his friend.
I was in my room.
I didn't hear anything.
I understand it got pretty loud.
You didn't hear anything?
My son is dead.
Leave me alone.
No one can bring
your son back, Rose.
But you don't want
to lose Danny, too.
If you'll just testify that you
heard Frank threaten Christine.
I told you, I didn't
hear anything.
Mr. Connolly, call
your next witness.
The state calls Christine
Hayes to the stand,
and asks that she be deemed a
hostile witness under the evidence code.
It is so deemed.
Mrs. Hayes...
would your characterize your
husband as a violent or abusive man?
Yes.
Did he physically abuse you?
Many times, yes.
- Did you ever call the police?
- No.
Ever file a charge against him?
No.
File for a divorce?
We had separated.
Mrs. Hayes, you want us
to believe that your husband
was a dangerous and violent
man who chronically abused you,
yet you never called the police
or filed a charge or divorced him.
Why is that?
Because he always
said that he was sorry...
that he had been working too hard
or was tired or had too much to drink.
He always said that it
would never happen again.
And I always felt that someday,
if I just held on long enough,
that he would change.
So, I stood by him.
- By having an affair?
- Objection.
Withdraw the question.
Mrs. Hayes...
we've heard that your
husband threatened to kill you
if he found you at home
at the evening of June 9th.
Did you believe him?
I was very scared.
Then, of course, you
called the police this time?
No.
You feared for your life,
yet you didn't think that
your husband's threat
warranted one call
to the police, did you?
Tell us, where were you at the
time that your son shot your husband?
- In the house.
- Doing what?
Cooking? Vacuuming?
On the phone?
- With your boyfriend?
- Objection.
You weren't scared
at all, were you?
Mr. Connolly.
You did nothing
to protect yourself
because you didn't think that
your husband's threat was serious.
Your son didn't think it was serious.
And, in fact, the threat was not serious.
Mr. Connolly!
No. No, that is not true.
I'm done here.
Mr. Matlock?
No questions at this
time, Your Honor.
The witness may step down.
This appears a good
time to break for lunch.
This court is in
recess until 2 P.M.
It's better than being in jail.
Yeah.
Danny...
I think I'm going to have
to put you on the stand.
It's very risky.
It opens you up to
a cross-examination.
After we hear your
side of the story,
then you're going to have to
answer Mr. Connolly's questions,
and I have absolutely no control
over what he might ask you.
He sure went after Mom.
Yep.
Just like he'll go after you.
But you're the only witness who can
respond to Sam Parker's testimony.
It was very damaging.
So, what do I do?
Well, I want you to
tell about the night
your father brought
Sam Parker to the house.
I want you to tell
what really happened,
everything that was different
from what Sam Parker said.
All right. I can do that.
Mainly, I want you to
make the jury understand
the fear you had
for your mother,
and how certain you were that your father
would carry out his threat to kill her.
OK.
When Mr. Connolly questions
you, don't lose your temper.
OK.
You already lost it in
the courtroom once.
This is going to be tougher.
He's going to come at
you with everything he's got.
He's going to bait you.
He's going to provoke you.
He's going to try his damnedest
to make you lose your temper
so the jury will see you
as a hot-tempered kid
who hated his father and
couldn't wait to shoot him dead.
I didn't want to shoot him.
How can you sit
there and eat like that?
Like nothing is happening?
Like I told you, it's
lunch and I'm hungry.
Now, see, that's what
I was talking about.
Now you're mad at
me, and I'm on your side.
All right. I'm sorry.
Now, no matter what
Mr. Connolly says,
don't argue with him.
If there's any fighting
to do, let me do it.
OK, I understand.
Eat a little lunch.
Come on, it will help
you keep calm. Eat.
Danny, why did
you shoot your dad?
If I had let him go into that house,
he would have killed my mother.
How can you be
so certain of that?
He told her that he would
kill her the night before.
But your father had made
threats against your mother
on other occasions, hadn't he?
He would threaten to beat
her up... And then he would.
But he had never threatened
to kill her before, no.
Danny, you heard
Sam Parker's account
of what took place that evening.
Was it correct?
No.
In your own words, would
you give us your memory
of what happened that night?
I was in my room when my
father came home with Mr. Parker.
I remember that he
called out for my mom.
Come on, Sam, it's all right.
Chris?
It's Frank.
Frank, what are you doing here?
I've missed you, Chris.
Come on, ask Sam here.
You're all I ever talk about.
I don't remember that dress.
Is everything OK?
When my dad saw
Mr. Williams, he lost it.
You whore.
He's just a friend, Frank.
You're the one who said
we should see other people.
Get the hell out of my house!
Go, go.
OK, but I'll call you later.
As soon as Mr. Williams left,
my dad started moving
towards my mother
with this real scary
look in his eyes.
- Where do you think you're going?
- To bed.
You've been
disloyal to me, Chris.
You know my feelings about that.
Please... Please,
Frank, just go.
No, not till we have a
little talk in the bedroom.
Look, Dad, come on.
She asked you to go.
Just don't cause
any trouble, OK?
Don't you ever put your
hand on me like that again.
My dad turned around
and took a swing at me.
I ducked, and I guess
he just lost his balance.
That's when my father
looked up at my mother
with this look I'd
never seen before.
You're not my wife.
You're a filthy slut.
I'm going to make you pay
for bringing men into this house.
Leave. Just leave.
Oh, I'm going.
But I'm coming
back tomorrow night.
And if every piece of your
clothing isn't out of this house,
I'll kill you.
Did you call the police after your
father left the house that night?
Yes, I did.
My mom begged me
not to, but I did anyway.
What did you say to them?
I told them that my dad said
that he was going to kill my mom.
The police said that there was
nothing they could do about that
unless a crime was committed.
So, I hung up.
Did you leave your name?
No.
That might have helped.
Why didn't you try to get
your mother out of the house
before your father came back?
I did. I tried.
But she said the reason
she separated from my dad
was so that she wouldn't have
to be afraid of him anymore.
She didn't want to run.
Ah.
It sounds like...
your mother was less afraid of
your father's threats than you were.
My mom always thought that my
dad had beaten her for the last time.
She was always wrong.
Danny, are you
absolutely certain,
if you had not shot your father,
he would have
killed your mother?
I have never been more
positive about anything in my life.
No further questions.
Mr. Connolly?
Danny... what kind of
dad was your father?
He was... He was OK sometimes.
Sometimes, not.
Did he ever help you
with your homework?
Did he ever come out to
see you play Little League?
Did he ever take you
to the Braves games?
No, not very often.
He worked a lot.
All those years,
watching your friends playing catch
with their dads on their front lawns...
You must have
resented him terribly.
I didn't resent my dad.
Did you ever see your
father mistreat your mother?
Yes.
And that resentment turned
to anger, then hatred, didn't it?
I was angry, but I
didn't hate my father.
The night your father came
home with Sam Parker...
he didn't trip down those
stairs. You pulled him.
You threw him down, didn't you?
- I didn't mean to...
- Yes or no?
- Yes, but...
- Had he hit you?
- No, but he...
- He didn't hit you.
And you didn't call the
police, did you, Danny?
That's why they didn't have your
name, because you didn't call the police.
Yes, I did.
You knew your father wasn't
going to kill your mother.
He said that he would!
He was drunk, and he was upset
at seeing another man
in his house with his wife.
It was an idle threat.
He knew it. Your mother knew it.
- And you knew it, didn't you?
- No!
Oh, come on, Danny.
The police never
found any knife or gun
anywhere in your
father's possession.
- He would have strangled her!
- Admit it, you hated him.
You don't know
what I had to live with!
- You're glad he's dead, aren't you?
- Objection.
- Aren't you?
- Objection!
No further questions.
Thank you for seeing me, Rose.
You sounded
worried on the phone.
Now that you're
here, you look worried.
I am.
I'd like to tell you
everything will be okay,
but the fact is...
There's a good possibility...
You think Danny's going
to be convicted, don't you?
Ben doesn't think the
jury believed his testimony.
Why?
Ben's been reading
jurors' faces for 35 years.
He knows when they're not
buying a defendant's story.
What about my testimony?
Danny is your son.
The jury expects
you to protect him.
How long a sentence
could he get?
He's being tried as
an adult, Christine.
He could get... Life.
The defense calls
Rose Hayes to the stand.
Mrs. Hayes, I want to thank you.
I know you loved your
son Frank very much,
and I understand how
difficult this must be for you.
How many years did you
live with your son Frank,
your daughter-in-law Christine
and your grandson Danny?
Four years, last month.
And in those four years,
did you ever see or hear your son
and your daughter-in-law fighting?
Well, sometimes at night,
when I was in my room...
I heard them fighting.
Did you ever see your son
hit your daughter-in-law?
No.
Did Danny ever tell you that
he saw his father hit his mother?
Yes.
Mr. Matlock, does your
witness need a recess?
Rose?
No, thank you, Judge.
When Danny told you that he had
seen his father hitting his mother,
did you believe him?
My son works very hard.
He's under a lot of pressure.
I understand. Did
Christine ever tell you
that her husband
was hitting her?
She...
She always said
it was her fault.
Mrs. Hayes, were
you in the house
the night that your son brought
Sam Parker home with him?
I was in the kitchen.
Mrs. Hayes, there have been
two entirely different stories told
about what took
place that night.
I'd like you to give us your
memory of what you saw and heard.
Now, you were in the kitchen
when you heard your son's voice?
Yes.
But you didn't go
in and say hello?
He was very angry.
Mrs. Hayes, in all the years
you have known your son,
how many times have
you seen him that angry?
Oh.
My Frank was like his father.
Joe worked very hard,
and I know he loved me...
but sometimes...
he had a temper.
Your husband hit you?
He was always sorry.
And deep down,
he was a good man.
Just like Frank?
Yes. Deep down.
I see.
You haven't had it
easy, Mrs. Hayes.
But we must have an answer.
How many times
have you seen your son
as angry as he was the night he
brought Sam Parker to the house?
Never.
I'm almost finished,
Rose, I promise.
Did you hear your son
threaten to return the next day
and kill his wife if
she were still there?
Yes.
Were you afraid for Christine?
Nothing further.
I know that it's wrong to kill,
even someone like him.
But what if I hadn't,
and you were dead?
I had no choice, did I?
Oh, Danny, the fault is mine.
I should have reported
the abuse to the police.
I should have divorced
your father years ago.
I should have gone with you
the night you wanted
to take me away.
The jury's coming in.
Ladies and gentlemen of the
jury, have you reached a verdict?
We have, Your Honor.
On the charge of
murder in the first degree,
we find the defendant
Daniel Hayes not guilty.
Thank you, ladies and
gentlemen of the jury.
You're dismissed.
This court is adjourned.
I'm so sorry.
www.tvsubtitles.net